<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Topic 1 on GoWi.Fi</title>
    <link>https://www.gowi.fi/topics/topic-1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Topic 1 on GoWi.Fi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>yourname@example.com (yourname)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>yourname@example.com (yourname)</webMaster>
    <copyright>(c) 2017 Copyright GoWi.Fi</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 14:17:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.gowi.fi/topics/topic-1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The perfect combination: WifiMapper and GoWi.Fi</title>
      <link>https://www.gowi.fi/2017/10/05/the-perfect-combination-wifimapper-and-gowi.fi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 14:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>yourname@example.com (yourname)</author>
      <guid>https://www.gowi.fi/2017/10/05/the-perfect-combination-wifimapper-and-gowi.fi/</guid>
      <description>We have kept an eye on an exciting London based Startup called OpenSignal. They have tapped into the fact that the global use of smartphones is leading to the rise of a wide-spread mobile sensor network. They are calling it “one of the most exciting technological innovations of recent times.”
WifiMapper Recently they built WifiMapper, which they call “the best free-Wi-Fi database in the world,” which users can tap into to instantly to find the nearest (and best) free Internet service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a secure wireless network (WiFi) for your AirBnB guests</title>
      <link>https://www.gowi.fi/2017/10/03/how-to-create-a-secure-wireless-network-wifi-for-your-airbnb-guests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 16:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>yourname@example.com (yourname)</author>
      <guid>https://www.gowi.fi/2017/10/03/how-to-create-a-secure-wireless-network-wifi-for-your-airbnb-guests/</guid>
      <description>If you are renting out your home on AirBnB, Booking.com etc or have a small business you may want to offer free WiFi access for clients. To do that in a secure way you don’t want to connect them to your own local network (LAN) where you have your computers, NAS backup and IoT devices connected.
You want to have an isolated network that is only for your guests. In technical terms you have to create something that is called a VPN or VLAN - virtual private network or virtual local area network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does the iPhone support NFC?</title>
      <link>https://www.gowi.fi/2017/09/30/does-the-iphone-support-nfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 15:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>yourname@example.com (yourname)</author>
      <guid>https://www.gowi.fi/2017/09/30/does-the-iphone-support-nfc/</guid>
      <description>At GoWi.Fi we use NFC in our GoWi.Fi signs and have been bravely waiting for Apple to join everyone else in supporting NFC tags since Google added NFC functionality to Android in late 2010.
At WWDC 2017 in June Apple announced that iOS 11 would have support for reading NFC tags and NDEF messages.
With Apple’s event on Sept. 12th, 2017 Apple has finally announced the new iPhone 8 and the iPhone X.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>